thehealthymaven.com 2019-10-04

# Privacy Policy - The Healthy Maven

**Privacy Policy and Terms of Use**

TheHealthyMaven.com maintains this Site to provide general information to our visitors. All use of this Site is subject to the following terms and conditions. By accessing and browsing this Site, you agree to be bound by these terms and conditions.

This site and all content written and published by Davida Lederle/The Healthy Maven, LLC. is [protected under copyright](http://www.copyright.gov/fls/fl122.html) © 2019. What that means is that by ** ** law our recipes, photos and posts are our own and reuse or publication of any kind needs our permission.

This policy may change without notice. You should periodically check this page to stay up to date with the latest policy. This policy is effective February 24th, 2013. This policy was last updated May 23rd, 2019.

These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

**Website Visitors**

I use several methods to see how you interact with The Healthy Maven. I do this to improve the website and content for you. In doing so, I track specific visitors who visit my site, track the pages you visit on my site, and the websites you came from. This information is for me to improve and better The Healthy Maven. Statistics may be shared publicly, but personal information on my visitors is never shared.

We collect information from you when you subscribe to a newsletter, fill out a form, enter information on our site, or simply browsing the site.

We may collect personal information from you that you’ve voluntarily submitted to us, such as your name or email address. For example, you may voluntarily submit information to this website when signing up for newsletters or submitting a comment or submitting an inquiry via our contact form.

We may also collect anonymous information such as your IP address. Anonymous information consists of non-personally-identifiable data. For example, when you use our website, we can log your IP address, the device you are using, operating system, browser type, referring website, pages you viewed, time spent on our site, when you came to our site. We may also collect information on actions you take while visiting our website, such as what links or buttons you clicked on.

**Do we use cookies?**

The Healthy Maven may use cookies & tracking technologies depending on the features offered. Cookies & tracking technologies are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to this site, a visitor’s demographics, and understanding how visitors use this site.

Cookies are also to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved user-experience. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

We use cookies to:

  * Keep track of advertisements.
  * Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since everyone’s browser is a little different, look at your browser’s Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you turn cookies off, it won’t affect your user-experience.

You may have also subscribed to our newsletter. All newsletters sent may contain tracking pixels. The pixel is embedded in emails and allows an analysis of the success of our marketing campaign. These tracking pixels allow us to see when you opened the email, if you opened the email, and what links you clicked in the email. This also allows the website to adapt future newsletter content to the interest of the user. This behavior is strictly confidential and will not be passed onto third parties.

**Email Subscribers**

On The Healthy Maven you can opt to enter your email address to receive website updates on recent posts. I will never send you spam messages or give out your email address. We do not sell, trade, or transfer any personal information to outside parties. When you correspond with us through email, your email address and the contents of the email is retained. We provide the same protections for these emails as we employ in all information that we have received electronically.

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, follow the instructions at the bottom of each email and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.

**Third Party Disclosure**

Some of our advertisers may use technology such as cookies when they advertise on our site. The advertiser’s technology can send these advertisers information that may be contained in log files. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing Florida rental houses to someone who has been looking up airfare for Florida, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing home decor ads to someone who frequents home decor sites).

Display Ads: we may use a third-party vendor to serve content and advertisements on our website, which may use cookies, as noted above. The use of cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet.

Retargeting Ads: from time to time, we may engage in remarketing efforts with third-party companies like Google, Facebook, or Instagram, in order to market the website. These companies use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the website. You can find out more about their usage of cookies by locating their privacy policy.

**Sponsored Posts & Affiliate Programs Disclosure**

In order for me to support my blogging activities, I may receive monetary compensation or other types of remuneration for my endorsement, recommendation, testimonial and/or link to any products or services from this blog.

For your convenience, this website may provide hyperlinks to websites and servers maintained by third parties. Thehealthymaven.com does not control, evaluate, endorse or guarantee content found in such sites. Thehealthymaven.com does not assume any responsibility or liability for the actions, products, services or content of these sites or the parties that operate them. You should carefully review their privacy statements and other conditions of use. Your use of these sites is entirely at your own risk.

**Here’s what that all means for you:**

I occasionally post affiliate links. These links may be for various products that I personally use, ebook bundles, and other similar products from bloggers or Amazon.

Know that anything I endorse on this blog, even if it is paired with an affiliate link, I am endorsing because I truly think the product is great, it is one that I use, and I want to pass on the information to you, my readers. I’ll never endorse products that I don’t personally use. I am not paid to write one way or another, and I choose which products I endorse, no one chooses that for me. Buying products through these links allows for me to maintain and grow The Healthy Maven, and I greatly appreciate your support.

Sometimes some pretty great companies reach out to work together and either compensate me for my time or provide me with free material. I will  _never  _endorse a product that I don’t fully stand behind or think would benefit the audience of The Healthy Maven, and I will always share with you when a post is sponsored. All opinions are 100% my own.

The Healthy Maven is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for us to earn fees by linking to [ **Amazon.com**](https://l.facebook.com/l.php?u=http%3A%2F%2FAmazon.com%2F&h=ATMnTKBCQpe5oFbNYFNVlZKeitIxWMuiO0d4zpPYzpL98uw66P6kBSlsmjKI0EP37Bc3wH51Npa8isbuf6wYUmcJtijtoLuaPtUYoU_EhfeUKZC8oOAPz3n6n7yKUJDmkiJ07ZizxB5xPQ) and affiliated sites. As part of this program, I can post customized links, provided by Amazon, to track the referrals to their websites. This program utilizes cookies to track visits for the purposes of assigning commission on these sales.

**Use of Photography and Recipe Sharing  **

You may view and print material displayed on this Site subject to the following conditions: (a) the materials may be used solely for your own, personal information and not for commercial use; and (b) you must retain without modification all copyright, trademark and other proprietary notices affixed to or contained in the materials you print and all copies thereof. You may not copy or otherwise use this Site or any portion hereof, except as expressly provided above. You may not reproduce, download, republish, frame, transmit, distribute, sell, license, modify, alter, reverse engineer or prepare derivative works from this Site or any portion hereof, except with the express prior written permission of Thehealthymaven.com. Use of data mining, robots and similar data gathering and extraction tools is expressly prohibited. Links to this Site should not be made without the express prior written permission of Thehealthymaven.com.

All recipes, photographs, and design on this site are the original creations and property of Davida Lederle. You are welcome to share a photo and link back to the recipe giving The Healthy Maven full credit. It is strictly forbidden to copy and paste the recipe in its entirety on your website without permission. For licensing inquiries for commercial use, general distribution, and publications, email Davida at Davida@thehealthymaven.com.

How you are welcome use the photography and recipes properly:

  1. Reprinting photos will full credit and a link to the post which it came from
  2. Modified recipe with full credit and a link to the post which it came from.
  3. Small excerpts (like listing of ingredients) without full disclosure of recipe (example would be listing ingredients – but not entire recipe).

If you have any questions about a photography or recipe request., please feel free to email Davida@Thehealthymaven.com.

**Accuracy of Information**

While Thehealthymaven.com uses reasonable efforts to furnish accurate and up-to-date information, Thehealthymaven.com does not warrant that any information contained in or made available through this Site (including, without limitation, any information provided directly by representatives of Thehealthymaven.com) is accurate, complete, reliable, current or error-free. Thehealthymaven.com assumes no liability or responsibility for any errors or omissions in the content of this Site or such other materials or communications.

**Disclaimer**

All recipes and information on this blog are of personal opinion only and not meant to diagnose or treat illness.  Please always consult your doctor about your diet and ingredients.

Thehealthymaven.com reserves the right to modify these terms and conditions at any time upon posting. By continuing to use this Site after any changes are posted, you acknowledge your acceptance of the revised terms and conditions. Please visit this page regularly to review the then-current terms and conditions to which you are bound.

### JOIN THE THM NEWSLETTER

Join 10,000+ members of the THM Community to get access to exclusive recipes, healthy lifestyle tips and behind-the-scenes news from our team!
